# **Farrel Adel Mohammad**

**Student Mentor** 

082131401640 (Mobile) farrel.adel@gmail.com https://farrel-portfolio.netlify.app/ Surabaya, Indonesia

## SUMMARY

I'm currently working as Kampus Merdeka Studi Independen - AI4IMPACT Apprenticeship's Student Mentor in Terra Weather Ptc. Ltd. Over the last 2 years, I have learned about HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Python, C++, and also React JS. I'm a curious, creative, efficient, and sociable person. I always want to learn new things.

#### EXPERIENCE

Student Mentor 07/2022 - Present

Terra Weather

• Mentoring 10 college student and helping them build chatbot.

Chatbot Developer 01/2022 - Present

Terra Al

- Foosh-bot (Chatbot for giving food recommendation)
- · TudungSaji (Chatbot for giving food recommendation)

# EDUCATION

Computer Science 2024

Universitas Pembangunan Nasional "Veteran" Jawa Timur - Bachelor's Degree

• GPA - 3.965

Science 2020

SMA Negeri 11 Surabaya

# CERTIFICATES

Fullstack Web Developer 2022 - Udemy 07/2022 - Present

Responsive Web Design - Freecodecamp 07/2022 - Present

Certificate of Completion Al4IMPACT Digipreneurfest Digital Bootcamp 2022 03/2022 - Present

## LANGUAGES

Indonesia Native English Basic